entstix.com 2013-06-11

# Privacy Policy Demo

**Privacy and Data Protection**

We only collect personal information about you (for example your name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card details) when you specifically provide us with such information on a voluntary basis, for example when purchasing or enquiring about event tickets online. Any personal information we collect via our web site will never be released or sold to any companies or individuals. We will not share your personal information for marketing or any other purposes without your consent unless where required by law. If you have registered your interest with us, and thereby given your consent, you may be contacted with relevant promotions, offers or information that you have expressed an interest in or that might be of interest to you.

**What we do with your information**

We use the information you provide us with to sell you the tickets you requested. We may occasionally use some of the same information (such as the type of tickets you requested) to tailor the content of this site to the interests of our users. By making a purchase from this site you are consenting to your financial and/or personal information being passed to any third party organisations necessary to process your transactions with us, such as credit card companies and banks. Except for these specific cases, we will never share financial information with third parties without your specific consent.

**Visitors to our websites**

When someone visits this website we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

**Use of cookies by this site**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

The table below explains the cookies we use and why.

**Cookie** |  **Name** |  **Purpose** |  **More information**  
---|---|---|---  
Google Analytics | 

_utma

_utmb

_utmc

_utmz

|  These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. |  [Click here for an overview of privacy at Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html "External link")  
Content Management System cookie |  AODSESSION |  This cookie is set by our content management system, upon arrival to the site. It is not used for any purpose. This cookie is deleted when a user closes their browser. |     
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "www.allaboutcookies.org").

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

**Security measures**

We take the security of your personal information very seriously. Consequently we use 1024 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption for all your transactions. This system encrypts all your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read if intercepted by a malicious third party.

**Third Party sites**

We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party sites linked to this site. Consequently we advise you to read their privacy policies before submitting data to such sites.
